Actually,
it's Mr. Lin Muyun,
the chairman of Lin Group,
who sent me here.
Wang Jiming?
His last name is Lin.
He is the biological son of Mr. Lin
and
the main heir
of Lin Group.
Lin Jiming?
Yes.
Wang Jiming is the eldest son of Chairman Lin Muyun.
Later he changed his surname to Wang after his mother.
The chairman has always been regretful
of driving them out of the house.
He hoped to recognize him
and let him inherit the Lin Group.
Wang Jiming has a half-brother
named Lin Jiming.
It may not be an accident.
But Mr. Lin suddenly had a stroke
and can't be reached now.
Wang Jiming
died unexpectedly.
It's useless to say anything.
Jiming.
Who benefits?
Who is suspicious?
Lin Jiming.
Hello.
Mr. Lin,
I've got the information
you asked me to look up.
Her name is Guan Tiantian,
and she's a lawyer.
A lawyer?
Yes.
And she's also
the lawyer for Zhao Zhiwei,
in his divorce case.
What a coincidence!
And in the previous
Tang's equity dispute case,
and the Huamao Land dispute case,
she was also
the lawyer of the other party.
That's interesting.
At 3 o'clock this afternoon,
it's the second court mediation
of Mr. Zhao's divorce case.
Mr. Zhao,
can you explain
whether the recording you provided
was obtained after violence
or coercion?
Nonsense!
I didn't hit her.
Absolutely not.
How could you not hit her?
Do you dare to say you didn't hit her?
I have a copy of
the hotel corridor surveillance video that night.
And the report
of the bed sheet test.
There are not only semen
but also blood.
You set me up.
This is the injury report.
Miss Bai has three old fractures of ribs,
and multiple contusions of soft tissue all over the body,
as well as injuries caused by hard objects.
The shape of the ring on your right hand
is consistent with the shape of the bruise.
Do you need to compare?
Zhao Zhiwei's case
should not be a civil mediation.
Lawyer Guan,
nice to see you again.
Lawyer Guan.
Mr. Lin,
nice to meet you.
The Tang's equity dispute case,
the Hua Maocheng land dispute case,
and now
Zhao Zhiwei's divorce case.
All three times,
the gun was pointed at our lawyer Guan.
This is intentional.
Oh.
Zhao's domestic violence injury
was instigated by the Lin's Group?
It's true that he hurt someone,
but he's a senior executive of our company.
If he goes to jail,
our company's projects
will be affected.
Name your price.
You want to settle now?
I need to talk to my client
about it.
That's not necessary.
She'll definitely listen to you.
Two million.
That's a lot.
Fine.
I'll think about it.
Take your time.
Hey.
Last night...
We're both adults.
Are you
expecting me to take responsibility?
No.
I just want to give this back to you.
Can I have your number?
Actually,
you look better in black.
It makes you
more approachable.
Hello,
Mr. Lin,
the legal department just sent over
the legal assessment report for Zhao Zhiwei's previous project.
It suggests
changing the project manager immediately.
Liu Yaping
doesn't care about the company's interests, right?
Then let's start with the legal department.
Mr. Lin,
I'll be here waiting for you.
Okay.
No need.
Just tell Ms. Guan I came by today.
Mr. Lin.
Welcome.
How did you find my humble place?
You're too busy.
I'm afraid my small case
can't get in line.
Small case?
Zhao Zhiwei's case is not simple.
Lead the way.
Let's talk about the details.
Sorry, Mr. Lin.
My schedule is
fully booked today.
Unless
you can find a way
to cut the line.
Yundong Club.
My treat.
I'll have the driver pick you up at 8.
Are you free?
Yes.
Hey,
why didn't you text me on WeChat?
I've been too busy
to check my phone.
Alright.
Thank you.
Guan,
I've accepted
your two-million offer.
Mr. Lin,
I have a new offer.
I want the position
of the general counsel of Lin Group.
From now on,
all the cases of Lin Group
will be mine.
What's your bargaining chip?
I can not only
help you solve the case of Zhao Zhiwei,
but also help you solve
all the troubles of the company.
And I
need the position of the general counsel of Lin Group
to enhance my value.
You should
think more about the future.
Right?
I'll think about it.
I'm waiting for your good news.
Can I add you on WeChat now?
Of course.
Hey,
Mr. Guan,
someone's looking for you.
Who is it?
Her name is
Liu Yaru.
Nice try.
Ms. Liu,
if you're here for legal advice,
please make an appointment.
If it's personal,
I'm sorry,
I'm very busy.
Stop pretending.
Stay away from Lin Jiming.
Who are you to warn me?
I'm his girlfriend,
he confirmed it himself.
Or is it just your wishful thinking?
You...
I've seen plenty of women like you,
using your body
to
climb the ladder!
Ms. Liu,
losing your temper won't solve anything.
I have work to do.
Excuse me.
How dare you be so arrogant?
Jiming.
Mr. Lin.
What brings you here?
What are you doing?
What's the fuss about?
Jiming, don't trust her.
This woman is trying to seduce you.
I'm helping you clean up the mess.
Help me?
You broke into my office
and harassed my legal counsel.
Is this what you call helping me?
I...
Mr. Lin,
please don't blame Ms. Liu.
She's just looking out for you.
I'm fine.
Ms. Liu,
it's just a misunderstanding.
Liu Yaru,
I'll say it again,
we're
not together anymore.
If you keep harassing Guan Law,
don't blame me for hurting your family.
Hmph!
Are you alright?
I'm fine, Mr. Lin.
You texted me
just to let me watch this show?
It seems that
you can't get rid of
Ms. Liu so easily.
What does this have to do with you?
It affected me.
What?
It affected my mood.
Generally speaking,
I wouldn't
get involved in this kind of thing.
Guan Yu,
if you can do
what you said,
the position of the general counsel of Lin Group
will be yours.